

NGUYỄN HƯƠNG Software Developer / Writer / Editor

Technical skills:

Software Development:

2 years

HTML, CSS, SCSS



1 year

JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJs, NextJS, RESTful API



3 months

Java, Python, JSP, Postman, Firebase, JSON, BIRT report, Angular, SQL, JQuery



1 months

Vue, C#, MongoDBXML



Project Management:

Project Management Models: SCRUM, AGILE, Waterfall,...



Git, Github, Gitlab, Trello



Figma



Editing:

- 0961578499
- dieuhuong2h@outlook.com
- 101A Phuong Mai, Ha Noi
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/huong-nguyen-dieu-393793200/

SUMMARY

I have been designing and creating websites for over 1 years. I have experience designing and writing websites mainly in ReactJS, and have skills regarding video editing, writing and photoshop!

I'm looking to join an inclusive company which doesn't discriminate peoples based on their race / gender / culture as a freelancer / salaryperson!

My English proficiency includes good communication skills in both listening and speaking, and the ability to read and write documents in English.

Additionally, I am proficient in using project management tools such as Git, IDEs such as Visual Studio Code, utilizing various assistant AI tools, and various designer tools such as Photoshop, Figma, and can do a bit of sound / video editing!

WORK EXPERIENCES

04/2023 - 09/2024

EMPLOYEE AT FPT FIS | Fresher / Employee

- I gained valuable experience collaborating and contributing effectively as part of a team, working on both front-end and back-end tasks to create an <u>User Management Platform</u> for a Real Estate Company.
- I honed my skill in React.js development and experienced in utilizing various other front-end tools, backed by practical work experience in a professional setting.

04/2022 - 07/2022

FRESHER AT CMC GLOBAL | Fresher

- During this job, I became familiar with corporate procedures and completed online courses to enhance my skills.
- Additionally, I gained valuable insight into teamwork and developed the ability to effectively contribute as a member of a team. I also involved with a <u>blockchain</u> project to enhance my ReactJS / NextJS skill.

01/2020 - 04/2020

INTERNSHIP AT FSOFT | Intern

- I had the opportunity to immerse myself in various office tasks and environments, allowing me to gain valuable work experience, learn about work ethics and responsibilities.
- I also had the chance to work with tools like Git and utilize popular Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) such as NetBeans, VSCode, and PyCharm, which provided me with valuable hands-on experience.

EDUCATION

Photoshop and designing tools







6 months

Video editing







3 months

Audio editing



Soft skills:

Native or bilingual proficiency

Vietnamese









Professional working proficiency

English







3 months

Voice Acting







09/2017 - 4/2023

understanding.

FPT UNIVERSITY - HOA LAC | Software Engineering Major My degree was focused on technical skills, including practical and theoretical knowledge, for Software development in both Frontend and Backend applications. In addition, this course taught me analytical skills and mathematical

Through this course, I developed the following abilities:

- Proficiency in using various programming editors and software, and building programs from scratch;
- Teamwork collaboration and project management skills;
- The ability to work independently by setting my own deadlines and managing my workload effectively;

PROJECTS

USER MANAGEMENT SYSTEM FOR DAT XANH GROUP

- I developed the Front-End of a User Management System for a real estate company, enabling managers to handle employee account details within the company's database.
- Utilized BIRT technologies to generate Excel reports based on specified inputted parameters
- Technologies used: ReactJS (class components), HTML/CSS, Javascript, Java **Spring Boot**
- Images of the project: https://imgur.com/a/AC7v9UZ

MORE INFO

- My Github: https://github.com/duyhung2h
- · Examples of my writings: https://shorturl.at/zRGBQ
- Video Editing Examples: https://shorturl.at/JoVoW
- Examples of my voice acting:

